<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Wolf & the Gang]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Wolf & the Gang]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/wolf-and-the-gang/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 20:19:07 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/wolf-and-the-gang/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blog]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Blog</h1><p>In March 2014 the OM Ship “MV Logos Hope” had made it’s way to Hong Kong and we left after nearly three years of service with the ship in South East Asia and the Arab World. Lisa is from Switzerland and I’m from Austria, so the logical questions were: Where would we live? Where would we have sufficient income and a place to stay that we could afford after three years of service with no income. A nice apartment in Vienna and some other factors brought us to the the decision that we should settle down in the one of the worldwide best “worth to live in” cities, Vienna, the capital of Austria and where I was born and had grown up – but God had different plans for us.
Friends from the Logos Hope had sent us an e-mail saying that Mercy Ships were looking for a Communications Manager for their ship Africa Mercy. In April 2014 I had the impression that I should send an e-mail to Mercy Ships just to honor the hint and to “checkmark” this topic which I couldn’t get out of my head. Everything went as expected – nobody from Mercy Ships gave a sign of life and I forgot about the whole thing. Until end of May when an e-mail arrived that stated that the position was still vacant and I should apply.
</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wolf-and-the-gang/blog/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f4bb934f-50a8-4129-bc53-68937e9303d2</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 20:19:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About</h1><p>Wolfgang, the older guy who constantly wonders why God always has the better plan in store</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/187283103e1bb291d75643bdeea11ec599ee7415.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/wolf-and-the-gang/c0f8811b-5ce9-425c-bf82-d33366768755/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c0f8811b-5ce9-425c-bf82-d33366768755</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 10:22:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>